Rocket Hunter is a war, action film directed by Christopher Forbes.
In one of the most dangerous missions of the war, an American B-17 pilot volunteers to fly a surrendered Messerschmitt 109 on a daring
flight through the heart of Germany to try to prevent the people of London from being terrorized by the V-2 rockets.
"Rocket Hunter" tells the story of an amazing pilot and his bombardier brother from the time they
are teenagers dreaming of taking to the skies to the dark days of January 1945.
Rocket Raccoon, commonly referred to simply as Rocket, is a fictional character in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU)
media franchise voiced by Bradley Cooper and based on the Marvel Comics character of the same name.
Rocket was based on movements from Sean Gunn and an actual raccoon named Oreo.
Rocket is a hot-tempered mercenary and weapons expert who, along with
his companion Groot, joins the Guardians of the Galaxy.
They then come into conflict with Ronan the Accuser and Ego.
Following the Blip, Rocket remains on Earth as a member of the Avengers.
Five years later, Rocket and the Avengers quantum time travel to
alternate universes to find the Infinity Stones.
Following their success, Rocket joins the battle against an alternate Thanos, and
rejoins the Guardians after their victory; departing for space.
Later, he and the Guardians make their base on Knowhere before coming
into conflict with Rocket's creator, the High Evolutionary.
Rocket then assumes leadership of the Guardians of the Galaxy.
Rocket made his first appearance in Guardians of the Galaxy (2014), and has become a central MCU character, appearing in six films as of 2024, in two
episodes of the I Am Groot series of animated shorts on Disney+, and in the TV special The Guardians of the Galaxy Holiday Special (2022).
The tone is dark.